我问你们
Let me ask you
现在为何都只用小灯泡啦
Why is everybody using these tiny, little lights nowadays?
我记得以前都用大灯泡啊
l remember when people used big lights.
钱德勒爷爷话当年
That's a good story, Grandpa.
莫妮卡让别人布置她的圣诞树
Wow. Monica's letting other people help decorate her tree?
是谁又把她灌醉了吗
Did someone get her drunk again, or...?
圣诞节的意义不在于完美的圣诞树
Having a perfect tree is not what Christmas is about.
而是在于与所爱的人共度
lt's about being with loved ones.
真好  布置好了
That is nice. And we're done. Ta- da!
我总觉得它少了一股圣诞味
lt just doesn't quite feel like Christmas to me.
那这样呢
Oh, here.
这样才像圣诞节嘛
See, now it feels like Christmas.
这就是犹太陀螺的由来
And that's the story of the dreidel.
有些人说圣诞树源自古埃及
Now, some people trace the Christmas tree bace to the Egyptians...
在每年白昼最短的日子
...who'd bring green palm branches into their huts
他们会把棕榈枝带进屋里
on the shortest day of the year...
象征生命战胜死亡
...symbolizing life's triumph over death.
那是四千年前的事了
And that was, like, 4000 years ago.
你开始讲故事也差不多是那时候
Around the same time that you started this story.
-你们好  -乔伊
- Hey, you guys. - Hey. What's up?
我不出门不行
l had to get out of the apartment.
吉宁在家里到处拉筋
Janine's stretching all over the places.
一转头就看到她在...
Everywhere l look she's like....
难怪你无法抗拒
l can see why that's hard to resist.
我好喜欢她
l like her so much.
可惜她对你没感觉
l'm sorry she doesn't feel the same.
就是啊  她好可爱
l know. And she's so sweet.
我好想喂她吃葡萄  帮她梳头
l just want to feed her grapes and brush her hair.
你知道她不是猴子吧
You are aware that she's not a monkey, right?
我已经不在乎吉宁了
l am so over Janine.
我之前觉得她很火辣
Yeah, at first l thought she was hot,
现在她已经成了过眼云烟了
but now she's like old news.
-你们好  -吉宁
- Hey, guys. - Janine!
我刚接到一个
I just got a call to be a dancer
除夕特别节目的通告
on a television special for New Year’s Eve.
叫什么狄克摇滚狄奇之夜的
lt's called some sort of Dickin' Rockin' Dicky Eve.
慢着
Hold it.
是狄克·克拉克新年摇滚之夜吗
Are you talking about Dick Clark's New Year's Rockin' Eve?
我不是这么说的吗
Yeah, that's what l said.
天哪  我们爱死那个节目了
Oh, my God, we love that show!
从我有记忆以来  罗斯和我每年都看
Ross and l have been watching it since l can remember.
内心深处的你仍是那个小胖妹对吧
You're still just a little fat girl inside, aren't you?
我今年要去当狂欢派对来宾
l'm gonna be one of the party people.
你要当去派对来宾吗
You're gonna be a party person?
那些人最酷了
Those guys rock the most!
他们叫我带人去
Well they said I should bring someone.
你愿意当我的舞伴吗
Do you wanna be my dance partner?
当然  我很愿意跟你跨年
Totally! l would love to spend New Year's with you.
明天就要录影了  我也不太懂
They're taping tomorrow. l don't understand why--
是这样的
Well, how it works is...
时代广场的部分是现场直播
...the part with Dick Clark in Times Square is actually live.
但他们会预录狂欢派对的画面
But they tape some of the party stuff ahead of time.
知道这事的人屈指可数哦
Not a lot of people know that.
你们也想去吗
Do you guys want to come too?
-真的还假的  -一言为定
- Are you serious? - We are there!
你笑什么笑
What are you laughing at?
我跟他是过去式了
Well, l used to date him,
但你还跟她还是进行式
but you're still going out with her.
谢谢...那我们就一起去
Thanks. Great, so we can all go together.
我得走了  回头见
l gotta run. l'll catch you later.
再见  吉宁
Bye, Janine.
她刚约我了对吧
Did she just ask me out on a date?
应该不是
l don't think so.
她找他参加千禧年最盛大的晚会耶
She invited him to the biggest party of the millennium.
但她也找了你和罗斯
Yeah, but she also invited you and Ross.
很遗憾  那应该不算约会
Yeah, honey, l'm sorry, l don't think that that was a romantic thing.
或许吧  但我有一个办法
Well, maybe. But, hey, l know how l can find out.
我们不是要参加跨年晚会吗
We're going to a New Yea's Eve party, right?
到了午夜  我可以亲她
So at midnight, l can kiss her.
要是她也回吻  漂亮
And if she kisses me back, great.
要是她说"你干什么"
But if she says 'dude, what the hell are you doing?'
我就说"新年情不自禁嘛"
l can say, "it wasn't me, it was New Year's."
比高中时罗斯亲我的理由好
Well, That's better than Ross kissing me in high school
他说他需要护唇膏
and saying that he did it because he needed Chap Stick.
那天很干燥嘛
lt was a dry day.
我们要上狄克·克拉克跨年晚会
We are going to Dick Clark's New Year's Rockin' Eve!
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
我的天啊
听着  摄影棚我熟
OK, listen I've been on sets before,
让我教你们几个秘诀
...so let me give you some advice , alright?
虽然是上电视
lt's a show,
我们只管跳舞
but we're just dancing.
没什么大不了的
Okay? lt's no big deal.
最重要的是要保持冷静
lmportant thing to remember: stay cool.
-了解  -好的
- Got it. - Okay.
天哪  跟我梦想的一样
Oh, my God! lt's just like l dreamed it!
全体集合
Everyone! Gather up!
-借过  -借过
- Excuse us! - Excuse us!
接下来的流程会是
Here's what's gonna happen.
音乐一放  你们就跳舞
The music's gonna start,you're gonna dance
我们会录影  不要看镜头  有问题吗
We'll tape it. Don't look at the camera. Any questions?
我有  什么时候播出
Yeah, l have a question. When is this gonna air?
好  你们去那边跳
Yeah. Now, you guys dance over there...
你们去那里  你们两个在这里
...you guys, over there. l want you two here.
其他人散开
Everyone else, spread out.
所以是什么时候播啊
So when is it gonna air?
你找厨房  我找后面的柜子
Okay phoebe, you look in the kitchen, I will look in the back closet.
不必浪费时间了  我在这里
l can save you time, ladies. l'm right here.
钱德勒  你一边去吧
Yeah. Chandler, why don't you take a walk?
这件事与你无关
This doesn't concern you.
我们在找莫妮卡送的圣诞礼物
We're looking for our presents from Monica.
什么  太差劲了
What? That's terrible!
不会啊  我们每年都找
No, we do it every year.
那就不差劲了啊
Oh, well, that makes it not terrible.
但我们没有找到过
No, yeah, we never find them!
她老是打败我们  奸诈的巫婆
She's always bested us, that wily...minx.
放心  我们找个一小时
Don’t worry, we’re just gonna search here for an hour,
就会换到乔伊那边找  好吗
and then we'll go to Joey's and search, okay?
不好  你们不能找她要送的礼物
No, not ok. You can't look for Monica's presents.
我们一定要找
But we have to!
你们不一定要找  也不能找
No. You don't have to. And you can't,
因为我也住在这里
because l live here too.
那你应该跟我们一起找
Well, then you should look with us.
为什么
Why?
你都不愁要送莫妮卡什么吗
Chandler, aren't you worried about what to get Monica for Christmas?
不会  我有个很棒的构想
No, I have a great idea for a present for her.
就只有很棒的构想
Oh, that's it? A great idea? Oh, yeah?
钱德勒  那是不够的
Chandler, that's not enough.
要是她送你一个大礼
I mean what if she gets you a great present
两个普通礼和一堆小礼呢
two mediums and and a bunch of little presents?
而你只送她一个大礼
And you just get her one present?
她一定会很难过
I mean that's just gonna make her feel bad.
你为什么要让她难过  为什么
Why would you do that to her, Chandler? Why? Why?
-有我帮忙找得更快  -没错
- If l help, we can find them faster! - Right!
逮到一个了
We have a live one!
-是梅西百货的袋子  -太棒了
- Oh, it's a Macy's bag! - Yeah.
这是给谁的啊
Who's it for?
"亲爱的废柴  我有可能会藏沙发下吗
"Dear losers, do you really think l'd hide presents under the couch?
附注  钱德勒  我就知道你会妥协"
P.S. Chandler, l knew they'd break you."
她可能已经发现了
Uh- oh. She may be onto us.
我们今年一定要找到
We are so gonna find them this year.
你们刚才说会到对面去找
You said you'd go across the hall and look.
该不会是每年都去吧
Do you do that every year?
是啊
Yeah.
你们没有到我的柜子后面
You don't go into the back of my closet
翻我的健身袋底下吧
and look under my gym bag or anything?
-没有  -从来没有
- No.  - No. Never do that.
那些事乔伊托我保管的东西
That's where Joey gave me stuff to store that
我看都没看过
l've never seen before in my life!
刚才的事只是幻觉
Okay, that did not just happen.
又有摄影机来了
Here comes a camera.
好  小意思  放轻松
Right. No biggie. Stay loose.
他们为什么一直避开
Why do they keep doing that?
想上镜头
If we wanna get on camera,
就得上那些平台
we have to get up on one of those platforms.
他们一直拍平台上的人
They’ve been taping those people up there all day.
没错
Right.
你们为什么能上去
What'd you guys do to get up on there?
我们有练过
We learned how to dance.
你练舞时也忘了穿内裤吗
When you learned to dance, did you forget how to put on underpants?
对啊
Yeah!
-你跳得很好嘛  -是吗
- Hey, you're a good dancer. - Really?
臀部再放松一点会更好
Yeah, well you’d be better if you just loosened your hips a little.
-怎么说  -像这样
- What do you mean? - Like this.
就是这样  跟着节奏摆动  好多了
That's it. Feel the rhythm. That's better.
你去跟那个女生跳
You're dancing with her.
-我们是一起的  -对  我们是一起来的
-  No-no-no-no-no we came together! - Yeah, we came together.
我看不出来
l don't see it.
你去跟那个高个子跳
You are dancing with the tall guy over there.
高个子  举手
Tall guy, raise your hand!
不...老兄  拜托让我跟她跳
No-no hey buddy, please let me dance with that girl,
我很喜欢她  我觉得我有机会
I really like her and I think I have a shot.
你觉得有  我觉得没有
Really, you think so? l don't.
乔伊那里什么都没...慢着
l couldn't find anything--  Hey, wait!
我们找到了
Yeah, we found them.
在客房衣橱的外套后面
They were in the guest room closet behind some coats.
你不必担心了  都是些烂东西
You have nothing to worry about because they're all crap.
那是我要送给你们的礼物
Those are my gifts, I got those for you.
谢了  好棒喔
Oh. Thanks, Chandler, they're great!
这个奇怪的金属AZ是什么
Chandler, what is this very weird metal A- Z thing?
那是书挡  是很棒的礼物
Those are bookends. That's a great gift.
好  抱歉  谢谢你送的AZ[音近屁股ass]
Oh. Okay, l'm sorry. Thank you for my "az."
记得放回衣柜里  好吗
Make sure you put all that stuff back in the closet.
好...
Yes, okay.
对了
Yes, okay, oh, by the way, I just gotta say,
你人真好
I think it's really nice of you
都搬家了
that even after you've moved,
还帮乔伊保管东西
you still keep storing that stuff for Joey.
喂  舞女
Hey, dancing girl?
我想上厕所
Can l go to the bathroom?
来转一下.好了
Here we go. Yeah.
很不错喔  盖勒兄妹
Looking good, Gellers!
还用你说
We know!
你看那个跩人
see that snippy guy over there?
他是指定谁上平台的人
He's the one who decides who gets up on the platform.
-我们应该去他面前跳  -好
- We should go dance by him. - Okay.
全部暂停
Okay, everybody, hold!
接下来的平台舞者有...
Next on the platforms are....
你们两个  还有...
You two! And....
-你们两个  -太帅了
- You two! - Cool!
请问一下
Excuse me, sir?
如果我不穿内裤会入选吗
Would it help if l weren't wearing underpants?
莫妮卡
Monica!
会吗
Would it?
高个子
Hey! Tall guy!
我想跟你聊聊
Listen, I wanted to talk to you about that girl
你的舞伴
that you're dancing with.
她真不赖  幸好我最后没带老婆来
She's nice, huh? To think l almost brought my wife to this.
是啊...好
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
老兄  我和她是一起来的
Uh, look buddy, I came with that girl, okay?
我想在倒数时吻她  我想追她
And I had this plan to kiss her at the new years countdown
所以能不能...
l'm trying to win her over, you know, so I was wondering if..
不行
l don't think so.
拜托啦  你可以跟我的舞伴跳
Oh come on man, you can dance with my partner,
她跳得风骚热辣
She's real mellow.
你在跟这个女生交往吗
Look, you dating this girl you came with?
我希望过了今晚可以...
l was hoping after tonight that maybe l could....
那就是公平竞争  抱歉
No. No. She's fair game if you ask me. Sorry, buddy.
好吧
All right. Hey.
公平竞争  你说得对  我还能说什么
Fair is fair. When you're right, you're right. What can l say?
你是小学生吗
Are you in second grade?
尿裤子的是你
Hey, man, you're the one who wet his pants.
真讨厌
Man, this sucks.
要是跟爸妈爱现完却没上电视
lf Mom and Dad don't see us on TV after we made them so jealous
到时候逊的就是我们了
then who's gonna be the losers then?
我知道怎样可以上平台了
l know what'll get us up on a platform.
怎样
What?
跳招牌舞
The routine!
我们最后一次跳都是中学的时候了
Ross, We haven't done the routine since middle school.
等那个跩人看过招牌舞
When the snippy guy sees the routine...
搭都会帮我们搭一座
...he'll want to build us our own platform.
有那么赞吗
Was it that good?
我们得了兄弟姐妹组的特别奖
We got honorable mention in the brother/sister dance category!
假午夜快到了
lt's almost fake midnight.
我们还能怎样
Do we really have any other choice?
那好  来跳吧
Okay, let's do it.
爸妈会嫉妒死
Mom and Dad are gonna be so faced!
五六七八
Five, six, seven, eight!
接下来该谁上平台还用问吗
So do we really need to ask who's going up on the platform next?
不用  你们上去照样再跳一遍
Oh no. You get up there and do that again, exactly like that.
拍下来之后搞笑漏网片段播
Make sure get this. Dick will want it for the Bloopers show.
卡  全体注意
All right, cut! Listen up, everyone!
接下来是倒数计时
When we start again, it'll be the countdown to New Year
大家要兴奋点哦
...so l want to see everybody's excitement!
嘿
Hey, guy!
限你三秒钟之内离开我的舞伴
Hey, guy, you have about three seconds to get away from my partner.
怎么了
What's going on here?
你看他的裤子
Take a look at the guy's pants!
你是叫我们要兴奋点
You told us to show excitement,
但他也兴奋过头了吧
but don't you think he went overboard?
你变态啊  给我出去
What's the matter with you? Go!
滚啦  湿裤男
Yeah, take a hike, wet pants!
你相信吗
Can you believe this?
进入千禧年时我们会在平台上
We're on the platform for the millennial moment!
就是啊
l know!
你没有偷练招牌舞吧
You haven't been practicing the routine, have you?
当然没有
No.
我也有
Me too!
回到现场时
When the music starts over again,
我还想跳机器人舞步
...l was thinking about maybe going into the robot.
罗斯  跳招牌舞就好啦
Ross, we should stick to the routine.
免得丢脸
We don't want to look stupid.
回到现场  倒数十秒
All right, we're back! Ten seconds left. Here we go.
十  九  八
Ten. Nine, eight.
七...好  这一刻终于来了
Seven. Okay, it all comes down to this.
一切顺其自然
Whatever happens, happens.
听天由命
Destiny.
三  二  一
three, two, one!
-卡  -不！
- Cut! - No!
快乐
Year!
新年快乐[no音似new新]
Happy "No" Year!
接着是时代广场的现场画面
Okay, here's where we go to the live shot of Times Square,
大家辛苦了  收工
Nice work everyone that's a wrap!
看我找到什么
Hey, look who l found.
你们好啊
Oh, hi, guys!
鸟类的方向感很好
You know, birds have a very good sense of direction.
或许它们可以帮忙找出礼物
l thought maybe they could help us find the presents are hidden.
如果礼物正藏在南方过冬的话吧
Yes, if the presents are hidden south for the winter.
顺着你的笑话去找也行
Or we could just follow your clever jokes.
笑话知道在哪里吗  当然不知道
Any ideas? Didn't think so.
来  把礼物找出来
Come on, show us where the presents are.
鸭子似乎认为莫妮卡送我垃圾
The duck seems to think that Monica got me garbage.
什么样的回礼能跟垃圾一样好
l wonder what l could get Monica that's as good as garbage.
我的AZ如何
How about my "az"?
-这是空心的  -什么
- Hey. This is hollow. - What?
这排座椅是空心的  我居然都不知道
This bench, it's hollow.
我居然都不知道
l can't believe l never knew that!
我们的礼物
Oh, the presents!
不  不要直视它们
Don't look directly at them!
什么
What?
没事  可以看
All right, no, we could look at them.
这是我的
This one's for me!
这是钱德勒的  拿去
This one's for Chandler. Here.
太好了  大包的是我的
And the big one's for me!
赶快拆来看  好
Oh, let's open them!
-等等  我们不能这样  -为什么
- Wait a minute. We can't do this. - Why?
我不想知道莫妮卡送我什么
l don't want to know what Monica got me. You know,
她一定很用心的替我找礼物
l'm sure she worked really hard at getting me a present,
想给我惊喜
and wanting to surprise me.
你们这样会破坏惊喜
And you guys are gonna ruin that.
我们得把礼物放回去
We have to put these back.
圣诞节不该这样
This is not what Christmas is about.
谁理你  我要拆我的
Whatever, Linus. l'm opening mine.
谁也不准拆
Nobody is opening anything, okay?
我不知道你们怎么想
Look, I don't know about you guys,
但我想看莫妮卡收到礼物的表情
l want to see the look on her face when l give her my present.
她一定也想看我收到礼物的表情
l'm sure she wants to see the look on my face when l get mine.
所以求求你们放回去
So, please, please, can we just...? Can we put them back?
-你会送我们更好的礼物吗  -好啦
- Will you get us better gifts? - Fine.
我回来了
Hey, guys.
你们找到礼物了吗
You found the presents?
钱德勒  你让她们找到了吗
Chandler, you let them find the presents?
帅啊
Great.
你知道那个滤水器多难找吗
Do you know how long it took me to find you that water purifier?
你送我滤水器啊
That's what you got me?
这下我懂了  你的表情真棒
Oh yes, I see what you mean. That look is priceless.
甜蜜的家
Home sweet home, huh?
回到现实真好
Nice to get back to reality.
我们也知道新年会怎样了
Plus, we know how the New Year's gonna go off.
千禧虫根本没什么嘛  对吧
l guess there's no reason for all that Y2K panic, you know?
好吧  晚安
Anyway, good night.
-乔伊  -怎样
- Joey? - Yeah?
三
Three...
二  一
...two, one.
新年快乐
Happy New Year.
为什么亲了我
What was that for?
今晚当他们喊卡  我们没能接吻
Tonight when they yelled "cut" and we didn't get to kiss...
我真的很失望  我真的...
l was really, really disappointed, and l just....
真的很想亲你
l just really wanted to kiss you.
真的吗
Really?
那时候我也很想亲你...那时候
ln the moment, l really wanted to kiss you too. ln the moment.
-那时候  -只有那时候
- ln the moment. - But only in the moment.
你...想再亲一次吗
So do you want to kiss again?
想啊  离除夕只有两个星期
Sure. New Year's Eve is only two weeks away.
你能等吗
Can you wait?
不能
No.
我也是
Me neither.
三  二...
Three, two....
乔伊  不必每次接吻都倒数
You don't have to count down every time we kiss.
好
Oh. Okay.
但我觉得我需要几秒钟做准备
Except l sort of felt like l needed a couple seconds to get ready.
我们在平台上  准备带全世界跳进千禧年
We were on the platform, ready to dance into the new millennium...
那家伙却喊了停
...and the guy yells, "cut!"
等等  你们真的跳了
Wait. So you guys are telling me that you actually did...
八年级的招牌舞步吗
...the routine from eighth grade?
对  不过当然得稍做修正
Yeah! But of course we had to update it a little bit.
你反应真快  知道要接住我
Hey, by the way, quick thinking about catching me.
我正想说  你们绝不可能
There's no way you could've done the end...
照以前的结尾跳
...the way you guys did it back then.
什么  当然可以
What? We could do it.
不行吧  你以前胖
l don't know. You were a lot bigger
我是说壮多了
l mean, stronger back then.
我可以  好吗
l can do it, okay?
来吧
Come on, let's go! Come on.
一二三四
One, two, three, four...
五六七八
...five, six, seven, eight.
我不行
l can't do it!
那样跳就铁定能上电视了
Now, you do that, you're on TV.